var riverQuestions = [
{//question 1:
question: "Which river is NOT a tributary of the Amazon?",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Madeira", "b) Jurua", "c) Cuito", "d) Negro"],
flags: [false, false, true, false],
answer: "c) Cuito"
},

{//question 2:
question: "Which river drains Lake Baikal, the world's deepest lake?",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Yenisei-Angara", "b) Sungari", "c) Ob", "d) Paraguay"],
flags: [true, false, false, false],
answer: "a) Yenisei-Angara"
},

{//question 3:
question: "What is the world's longest westward-flowing river?",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Colorado", "b) Nile", "c) Congo", "d) Amazon"],
flags: [false, false, true, false],
answer: "b) Congo"
},

{//question 4:
question: "Into what sea does the Volga River empty?",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Black", "b) Adriatic", "c) Caspian", "d) North"],
flags: [false, false, true, false],
answer: "a) Caspian"
},
    
{//question 5:
question: "In what country would you find the Murray-Darling River?",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Canada", "b) Australia", "c) Scotland", "d) South Africa"],
flags: [false, true, false, false],
answer: "b) Australia"
},
    
{//question 6:
question: "Which river flows over Victoria Falls?",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Congo", "b) Orange", "c) Nile", "d) Zambezi"],
flags: [false, false, false, true],
answer: "c) Zambezi"
},

{//question 7:
question: "In what country is the River Kwai, famous for its bridge?",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Thailand", "b) Japan", "c) Cambodia", "d) Mongolia"],
flags: [true, false, false, false],    
answer: "a) Thailand"
},
    
{//question 8:
question: "What river forms the eastern border of Luxembourg?",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Loire", "b) Rhine", "c) Moselle", "d) Rhone"],
flags: [false , false, true, false],
answer: "c) Moselle"
},
    
{//question 9:
question: "Which country's longest river is the Waikato?",
possibleAnswers: ["a) New Zealand", "b) Japan", "c) Chile", "d) Senegal"],
flags: [true, false, false, false],
answer: "a) New Zealand"
},
    
{//question 10:
question: "Which of these Polish cities is NOT located along the Vistula?",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Poznan", "b) Warsaw", "c) Gdansk", "d) Cracow"],
flags: [true, false, false, false],
answer: "a) Poznan"
},
        
{//question 11:
question: "Lisbon sits on which river?",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Esla", "b) Tagus", "c) Segura", "d) Douro"],
flags: [false, true, false, false],
answer: "c) Tagus"
},
        
{//question 12:
question: "In what country would you find the Guadalquivir River?",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Brazil", "b) Portugal", "c) Spain", "d) Ecuador"],
flags: [false, false, true, false],
answer: "c) Spain"
},

{//question 13:
question: "A river branch flowing away from the main stream of a river is called a _______.",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Distributary", "b) Estuary", "c) Tributary", "d) Drift"],
flags: [true, false, false, false],
answer: "a) Distributary"
},
            
{//question 14:
question: "What is the largest and most important river in Mozambique?",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Niger", "b) Nile", "c) Zambezi", "d) Congo"],
flags: [false, false, true, false],
answer: "c) Zambezi"
},
            
{//question 15:
question: "Which Canadian river system has the largest drainage area?",
possibleAnswers: ["a) Columbia", "b) St.Lawrence", "c) Mackenzie", "d) Yukon"],
flags: [false, false, true, false],
answer: "c) Mackenzie"
    }
];